activism.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy policy - Activism - Online Petition

**[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** recognises that your privacy is very important to you and that you have a right to control your personal information. We know that providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that seriously. This privacy policy forms part or our Terms of Use (TOU) and is subject to and should be read with our TOU.

Your email address will NEVER be displayed on this website.

We will not email you anything unrelated to **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")**. If your email address is supplied, it will be stored securely.

If you are signing a petition, you may be sent a signature receipt by email that confirms that you have signed the petition. The receipt is for your records and provides information about how to edit and manage your signature. Your email address may be used for signature verification by **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** when we conduct quality control of a signature list. This is important to maintain high standards of signature list integrity. Quality signature lists promote quality petitions and successful campaigns.

## Your information

**[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** will not give or sell your information to any third party. If signing a petition, your information can be accessed by the petition's author. Petition authors agree to use signatures responsibly, legally and in compliance with our Terms and this Privacy Policy. This may involve the author contacting you about the campaign you have supported at **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")**. Authors also have permission to forward petition signatures to the relevant petition's target, so petition targets may also ultimately view signature details. Authors agree not to republish petition signatures on any other website or public media forum.

## Signature and Signature Comment Display and Search Engine Access to Signature Lists and Signature Comments

If you are signing a petition your signature (and signature comment) may be publicly displayed in a signature list (and signature comment page). Each petition at **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** has a public signature list that publicly displays at **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** all those who sign each petition. Our public lists do not include email or street addresses, but may include your town/city. Comments made with a signature can appear on a dedicated signature comment page.

The public lists and comments give weight to each petition and confidence to other signers. Each author has the option to NOT display their list publicly. But you should assume that the author may display their list. If you choose our "Anonymous" designation feature, then your name will be cloaked publicly and will only be viewable to the author and target. You may also elect to hide your signature comment from public view if you only want the author or target to view your comment.

Please note that search engines such as Google and Yahoo may be able to view your signature and signature comment and may index your signature and signature comment (if made). You may prevent indexing by cloaking your signature with an "Anonymous" designation and by "hiding" your comment. **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** members may now edit their signatures (including comments) to encourage or hide from search engine exposure. For information about how to edit your signature please read our FAQ.

## Facebook comments

If you use the facebook comment facility on any petition then your name and facebook photo may appear on the **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** site. **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** uses a facebook plugin for the facebook comment facility. **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** does not guarenatee that attempts to edit facebook comments by users of this facility will result in the desired editorial results. Any use of the facebook comment facility is at the user's own risk.

## Advertisements on **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")**

**[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** uses the services of Google and Simply Advertising.

* Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Specifically Google uses the DoubleClick DART cookie.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

## Cookies

See info above. We also use some cookies to remember who you are. In addition, **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** uses cookies and scripting for several site functions. This information is used to enhance customer experience of our software.

## Signature Details and Personal Information

Signatures will include the signer's IP address which will be available to the author and **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** administrators for security reasons. Other information provided to **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** in the signature process will be treated according to international standards.

**[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** provides personal data access rights to all signers and others who leave personal information on the **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** website. **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** respects the data access rights of those who entrust information to the **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** website. **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** complies with International protocols in this regard. International standards allow for small administrative fees to be applied in some cases where records are requested or edits requested in relation to personal records.

## Business Transfers

By subscribing to or using the Services, User acknowledges and agrees that **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** is entitled to transfer User’s personal data to third parties.  
If **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** , or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy and that there may be changes to the policy.

## Email contact from **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")**

If you are signing a petition, you may be sent a signature receipt by email that confirms that you have signed the petition. The receipt is for your records and provides information about how to edit and manage your signature. You may also be sent an update about the petition you have signed. On an occasional basis, you may be sent infomation about related petitions and site updates. If you have joined during or after the signature process you may sent email that is relevant to your **[Activism.com](http://www.activism.com/ "Activism.com")** account.
